

Davis Nyakno-abasi

Software Developer

Talented individual with in-depth knowledge of designing, development tools and coding languages. Desirous of the role of Software Developer . to apply 2+ years of work experience in innovating software designs, testing and coding as well as debugging programs and troubleshooting and augmenting the company's reputation.

x nyaknodavis318@gmail.com



+2349036103607



Port Harcourt, Nigeria



github.com/nickdavis3188

WORK EXPERIENCE

Backend Developer 3Reen LTD Nigeria

07/2021 - Present

Lagos Nigeria

An Online company that allows people to buy and sell physical goods, services and digital products over the internet rather than at a brick-and-

payment gateway/API

- Building api for AUTH/Product insertion/ Payment gateway etc

Full Stack Developer KASG

05/2019 - 03/2021 Port Harcourt, Nigeria An Online company manage some data gotten from a drilling activities Api / frontend design

 Developed full-stack web applications which processed, analysed, and rendered data visually.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Statistics and Computer

University of Port Harcourt

09/2019 - Present

Port Harcourt Nigeria

Courses - Statistics and Computer

science

Software development Luthech

02/2018 - 08/2018

Port Harcourt Nigeria

SKILLS

Python(Django) jQuery Dat(Flutter) Software Development Team Building & Leadership MySQL

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

Hostel Roster Manager Amino Kano Hostel/University of Port Harcourt

02/2019 - Present Port Harcourt/Nigeria Amino Kano hostel Tasks/Achievements

- Write ,update and maintain computer programs or software packages for the hostel . This software tracks and manage each room in the hostel that maintain good qualities by doing sanitation on time and on their day

ORGANIZATIONS

Ken Saro-Wiwa Innovation Hub (02/2022 - Present)

LANGUAGES

English

Professional Working Proficiency

INTERESTS

community work or volunteering

Learning website design in my spare time

Lego Mindstorms and experimenting with artificial intelligence in LISP

Traveling